Thank you for all your hard
work this summer.
I'd like to start this staff meeting,
but right now,
Uchiyamada-sensei is busy.
He is taking an urgent call.
Did something happen?
It's Aizawa Miyabi's mother,
the president of the PTA.
It looks serious.
Of course!
I'm not sure what happened,
but Kotani-sensei suddenly said
she was going to cancel
the flower arranging course.
And Hakamada-sensei who
used to be so enthusiastic
about club activities has
ignored the clubs completely!
And then there's
Teshigawara-sensei, who left
in the middle of his special
advanced class in such a state!
After that... continuing was
out of the question.
The class that the head teacher
started as a replacement
was a disaster!
I told him not to do it.
It was too much out
of his expertise.
Wh-What did she say?
What did the PTA
president want?
For now, continue the meeting.
Well, now then...
This coming year, we are planing
to use new text books
starting from this fall.
I am carefully considering
the choices
from this list we compiled.
I will leave this up
to Nakamaru-sensei.
I'm sure no one has
any objections.
I understand.
Then I will take
responsibility for this.
- Excuse me...
- Yes?
Since we'll all be using these,
shouldn't we discuss this
a little more?
Well then, that is all
on the agenda for today.
Thank you for coming.
The PTA president said if
there are any more incidents,
she'd hold me responsible!
This principal's chair...
This is all Onizuka's fault!
I can't let him get away with this!
You just have to wait until
summer break is over, sir.
If class 2-4 doesn't end their
boycott by the start
of fall session,
then Onizuka will be fired.
That's right, isn't it?
Soon, that troll will disappear.
You're right!
Ah man, only two weeks
of summer left.
What are you so worried about?
Oh, I know, it must be one
of your students.
Are you having trouble again?
It's not that! You know,
summer is supposed
to be the season of love.
The way it's going,
this year's going end
- without anything happening.
- So you want some action?
What are you talking about?
What I'm talking about
is romance,
to make a wonderful
summer memory.
Well, whatever, but you're not
getting any younger.
You should do it soon.
Listen to yourself.
Don't you have any values?
You know, the tele-clubs
are the greatest!
When you meet a total babe,
you can go that same
day to a hotel.
On top of that, they're nineteen!
I think it was her first time...
I just want to share
the excitement with you.
I...
Hey now, listen,
I've decided that I will do it only
with the right woman!
Suit yourself.
Sorry, but I've got a date
tonight too.
Young girls are great you know,
such great bodies,
and so passionate!
Well, a virgin like you
wouldn't know.
Ah, get out of here!
Well, you could go get
a compensated date
with a high school girl.
He didn't touch his sômen...
Hello, this is Fuyutsuki.
Oh... this is Onizuka.
- What happened?
- Uh...
Um, well...
I was wondering,
maybe you're free today?
- Why is that?
- Well, see...
Wanna go get something to eat?
You know, we never had my
welcoming party yet.
Gee, what should I do...
Please.
Oh, all right.
We haven't had your
welcoming party yet,
and you might be fired
by fall session, right?
- Such a nice ass, hmm?
- Huh?
- What are you doing.
- You see, I -
when I see someone walking
around dressed like that,
I become concerned it may be
one of our students.
Since they're free for summer,
I'm worried they
may get involved with
inappropriate relations.
You may talk big,
but your nose is growing.
No it's not.
Do you think you can solve your
class' problems with an attitude
- like that?
- It'll be alright.
I wonder.
That time, just when Murai-kun
was about to tell you about
his secret, saying "When he's
ready to talk, he'll talk"
and trying to look so cool.
You know, it does no good
to force them to talk.
Maybe so,
but Murai Kunio and Aizawa
Miyabi started distrusting adults
after Murai-kun's good friend
was gone, right?
The key is to find out
about that, right?
I see.
- Do you know anything?
- Why ask me?
You were just saying...
The only thing I know,
two years ago, Murai-kun's
good friend dropped out.
After that, he died
in a motorcycle accident.
Since then, it seems that
subject has become taboo.
I see.
Okay then, let's do this...
Let's find a quiet park,
- and carefully discuss this.
- What?!
Or how about a hotel lounge?
Oh, but it might take until
morning, better get a room.
You know, just when I was
being serious...
Oh, wait!
Fuyutsuki-sensei,
how about dinner?
You're unbelievable!
Because you lost a test
of courage,
you were about to tell them?
Murai, run!
Listen,
maybe...
- we can trust Onizuka.
- What are you saying?
Have you forgotten why
Takeshi died?
It was because he was betrayed
by his homeroom teacher.
I'll never forget.
Why he died. About him.
I'll never forget till the day I die.
I'm not going to be fooled
by Onizuka.
Will you wait, Fuyutsuki-sensei!
Yo, Murai!
How's your mom?
Give her my best!
SORIMACHI TAKASHI
MATSUSHIMA NANAKO
KONDÔ YOSHIMASA
ENJÔJI AYA
NUMATA BAKU
KOBAYASHI MASAHIRO
IDA KUNIHIKO
IKEUCHI HIROYUKI
NAKAMURA AIMI
SHIRAKAWA MINAMI
HAYASHI TOMOKA
FUJIKI NAOHITO
MABUCHI ERIKA
TATEISHI RYÔKO
TAJIMA REIKO
TAKAHASHI KATSUMI
MIZUTANI ATSUSHI
ANZAI ERI
NAKAO AKIRA
SHIRAKAWA YUMI
English Subtitles by
STUDIO NEW MEDIA
Subtitles Edited and Timed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
AKABANE HIROSHI
A Production of
KANSAI TEREBI & AVEC
I love that!
Maybe...
we can trust Onizuka.
Oh man, I need money.
And we can't get jobs.
It would have been great
born rich.
My dad's just a salaryman.
- His last bonus was pathetic!
- Mine too!
Miyabi, it's great that your
family is rich, isn't it?
What's up? You've been
out of it tonight.
Yeah, is there something
worrying you?
It's nothing.
I was just wondering if there
was something
- we could do to Onizuka.
- Forget him already!
He's going to be fired
come fall anyway.
Right! As long as we
don't go to class.
You don't understand a thing,
that's why you say that!
What are you girls doing
out this late!
We're on our way home
from cram school.
- That's right!
- What's with those clothes!
It may be popular, but it's like
you're wearing underwear.
Don't you have any pride as
students of Seirin Academy?
You better not be doing any
compensated dating.
How rude! We would
never do that!
Then why are you loitering
around out here?
If you're so suspicious of us,
then you can give my
mother a call.
In any case, just because
it's summer
doesn't mean you can slack off!
If you're not careful, you could
get into a major situation.
What's with Nakamaru?
Don't you think he's acting
even bigger than usual?
Hey, wait!
Who's that guy kissing up
to Nakamaru?
That is so pathetic!
I think I'd die if
I became like that!
- What's wrong?
- That's... my dad.
- No way!
- Why's he with Nakamaru?
He sells teaching materials
and text books.
Chikako.
Cheers!
So, you were a high school
student until this March?
- That's right.
- That's not good!
Then you're not much different
than my students!
Sensei,
it's nice to come to a place
like this occasionally, isn't it?
It's been five years since you
separated
from your wife, hasn't it?
Raising a child takes so much.
That's right, so I have no time
to come to places like this.
Right? So let's live it up tonight!
Hey,
keep him company, now.
Nakamaru-sensei,
I don't mean to be so persistent,
but please, please consider
our text books.
- Yes, I know.
- Then,
if we could discuss the content
in more detail...
Lighten up, sir!
By the way, I heard.
- Congratulations!
- Hey, what's that?
You're going to be head
teacher soon!
Wow!
Where did you hear that?
It's still unofficial!
It's only natural!
Because you've make such
a great contribution
- to the school.
- Oh, you can tell?
As Head Teacher Nakamaru,
please consider our texts
for Seirin Academy.
I wonder, what should we
do to tonight?
Leave that to us,
please feel free!
Um, this girl is okay for tonight.
No, I couldn't, I'm a teacher!
It's alright. This girl is very
tight lipped.
That's right,
Nakamaru-sensei told us
at today's staff meeting,
they're going to purchase
new texts for this fall.
But you know, I wonder
if we really need to.
I thought our current text's
were still fine.
Can we stop talking about
things like that?
You know,
we're finally alone together.
And today's my welcome
party, right?
Then what should we talk about?
How about things like love?
Your just going to say let's go
to a hotel, right?
- You'd object to that?
- There you go again!
I told you before!
I've decided that my first time
will be only with
the woman I love!
And so...
What are you trying to say?
You see, I...
- See, I...
- Eikichi?
What are you doing here?
You're being so cold!
You never call!
- Oh...
- Who is this?
Oh, uh, nobody special...
I should ask who you are?
What are you to my Eikichi?
Hey, cut it out!
Don't talk like that!
Please don't worry,
I'm just a coworker.
I was just about to leave.
Hey, wait! Fuyutsuki-sensei!
Bye then... Eikichi!
Man, this pisses me off already!
I don't want to see my pathetic
dad already.
Hey Miyabi, is there something
cool we can do?
- How about a club?
- Oh, but I don't have money.
Me too.
Why don't we do some
- compensated dating.
- What?!
You said you wanted
money, right?
Then that's the easiest way.
Adults are so stupid.
Just flash them panties
and they'll give you money.
- Are you serious, Miyabi?
- That's crazy!
Silly,
once you get what you want,
just run away.
What?
I'm a seventeen-year-old
high school girl
who loves a good time.
I'm looking for a message
from a wonderful rich man.
I'm waiting!
Oh geeze, just a minute more...
What are you grumbling about?
Here.
You're sure your parents
aren't coming home?
Yeah. The Benz just came back
from the shop,
so they went to a onsen.
Why was it in the shop?
He left it at school
and someone trashed it.
Really? I guess there are evil
people in this world.
Kiss me!
- Please! Hey, hey!
- Hold on...
- We're home.
- Oh no, they're back!
- No way!
- Yoshiko, are you home?
Wait! We haven't done
anything wrong!
I'll introduce you to my dad
and mom.
- Don't be ridiculous!
- Wait!
- Who was that?
- Hm?
- Who was that just now?
- Who?
Don't play innocent,
they ran away just now!
Did you bring a boy in here
while we were gone?
Why'd you come back so early?
Well you see,
the ryokan was a disaster.
The food was terrible
and the baths dirty,
I don't know what dad
was thinking.
Well it was through
an introduction
of one of the school staff.
Never mind that!
Who was that that ran away?
It wasn't...
that guy Eikichi?
Oh! Why didn't you
introduce him?
That's what I told him.
I'll never approve
of the likes of him!
Never mind, Dad,
it doesn't matter.
Hold on Yoshiko!
That guy... Do you know
his last name?
Yes, I asked the other day.
Why didn't you tell me earlier!
So what is his name?
I forgot.
How can you forget something
so important!
Give me a break!
If you want to know so badly,
find out for yourself!
I'm pooped!
I'm going to take a bath.
- Hey, hurry up.
- I'll be right there.
- How'd it go?
- Perfect!
Me too!
They're so stupid,
it was so easy!
What about Chikako?
When it came to the moment,
she chickened out.
- Your kidding!
- Miyabi, I can't...
Have you forgotten our pact?
We made a vow to stick together
through anything, right?
I told you should just let
yourself loose.
Idiot! I told you I'm not going
to a prostitute the first time.
- Let's go.
- Stupid!
Tele-clubs aren't prostitution.
It like a dating service!
You don't know that?
That's why you never get any!
Me?
I'm a scout for a record
company.
Oh yeah! Komuro is like family
to me already!
What are you doing? Hurry up!
Make sure and read that.
Hello? Sorry about that.
Gee, is this for real?
- Hello?
- Hello.
I'm a high school student.
- What do you do?
- Me?
Well, I write scenarios
for dramas.
No way!
What have you written?
Let's see... Like Long Vacation,
and Love... Love Gen...
Love Generation.
No way! I loved both
those shows!
Oh, great.
Why the heck am I lying?
But you know, wasn't the writer
a woman for both those shows?
Oh, um, well...
That's a pen name!
You know, a pen name!
Wow! Then you get to meet
a lot of famous people?
Yeah, well it's part of my work.
Wow! So who have you met?
Yes, well...
Hey, why don't we get together?
Will you give me money?
If you give me money,
I'll meet you.
How much?
Hey! Over here!
Isn't 100,000 a bit much?
- Just hand it over!
- You better pay it back!
I've got it rough too, you know.
- Okay. See ya!
- Sheeze, did he hear me?
What are you doing? Let me go!
I see, so this
is compensated dater.
What about you?
You're a teacher
and you used a tele-club!
You got no right talking like that!
Besides, what's wrong
with compensated dates?
It makes the guy happy,
and we get money.
It doesn't bother anyone!
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
You serious?
Wow! So this is what one
of these hotel's is like?
Hey! There's even karaoke!
Hurry and get undressed.
Chikako, I've got one request.
What is it?
Before you get undressed,
put on loose socks.
What?
You know, our school doesn't
have loose socks, right?
Stop messing around.
Why doesn't you hurry
and take a shower.
You're going
to run away then, right?
You know...
When I do it, I really want
to do it with the woman I love.
Listen, Chikako.
If you do this, you'll come
to hate sex.
If you do it for money, then it
means you enjoy money
more than sex, right?
That would be terrible.
When you do it with
the person you really love,
it's the greatest
feeling you can have.
- Is this alright?
- Sure.
- Just pay up.
- I know!
- Hide!
- Why?
Just do it!
Let's see, Onizuka...
What am I worrying about?
She's my daughter.
There's no way she could be
fooled by a man like him.
I've done it, sir!
I've caught that Onizuka
red handed!
This will be the end of him!
You'll become principle for sure!
Nakamaru-sensei...
I'm counting on you.
Sir? Hello? Hello?
Looks like I can't count
on the head teacher either!
Looks like it's up to me
to save our academy.
TO MIYABI
TAKESHI
- Hello?
- Miyabi, I'm in trouble!
What happened?
Nakamaru saw us leaving
the hotel.
He told me to come to school
tomorrow.
Seriously?
I'm going to be expelled
for sure!
- I'm home.
- Hold on.
Why don't you figure something
out with the guy and fool them?
But the other guy...
- it's Onizuka.
- Onizuka?!
What should I do, Miyabi?
- I got a great idea.
- What is it?
Looks like the final straw,
Onizuka-sensei.
For a teacher to engage
in adulterous acts
with his student, what do you
think you're doing!
We didn't do anything improper!
- Right, Chikako?
- Don't play innocent.
I saw it with my own eyes!
I saw you two leaving
the love hotel.
Nakamaru-sensei,
why where you there too?
Yes, well, I just had someone
visiting and was showing
them around town.
Th-That's why
I discovered you two!
That was a extracurricular
lesson.
What's that?
I took her to a love hotel
to show her
the difference in love.
No one's ever going to believe
something so ridiculous!
Chikako, say something.
Go on, is there something you
want to say?
I...
Come on, Chikako.
We didn't do anything,
so just go ahead and tell him.
I... Onizuka-sensei...
Onizuka-sensei forced
himself on me!
What was that!?
That was great, Miyabi!
Now Onizuka'll be fired for sure!
Yeah, well.
Man, I wish I could have
seen his face!
What's wrong?
You know, Onizuka...
- He didn't react at all.
- What?
No matter what I said,
he just stood there and listened.
He just gave up.
He knew he couldn't
make excuses.
Maybe.
Could you be feeling guilty?
No, but...
Or maybe you really did
do it with Onizuka.
- What are you saying!
- You wanted money, didn't you?
You probably got caught up
by Onizuka.
Miyabi, how can you say that!
- That's terrible, Miyabi!
- Don't you talk back to me!
When we go to concerts,
or go out to eat,
it's always my treat.
And when we have tests,
if I never showed you
my answers, you'd never pass.
And this time too.
If I didn't rescue you,
you'd have been expelled,
you know.
Or would you rather
have had that?
Chikako, wait! Chikako!
You can't do anything
for yourselves.
Don't go talking big.
Yes?
Oh, Fuyutsuki-sensei!
Could you hold on a minute,
it's a mess.
- Right here is fine.
- Huh?
- Why the scary face?
- What do you expect!
Causing such a problem!
Not to worry,
I haven't done a thing.
Do you think I can believe such
a habitual prankster?
Like last time, you had that girl
fawning over you
calling you Eikichi.
How can you expect me to trust
a person like that?
Uh, well, hold on a minute.
I haven't used it yet.
Not good enough?
Then...
Why don't you say anything?
Why don't you defend your
innocence?
Ôshima Chikako's lying, right?
Those who lie will eventually
tell the truth.
Besides, I believe in her.
Hello, this is the Ôshima's.
Oh, Nakamaru-sensei!
Thank you for the other day!
Thank you very much!
I will deliver the text's to your
school tomorrow.
It's about a gratuity...
Oh yes.
I am certainly grateful
for your business.
That's not what I mean.
You know...
I have a hard time with expenses
like the loan on my condo.
That's why I gave you my
account number.
- He's taking a kickback!
- But...
I can't...
That's alright if it's too
much for you.
I can always switch to another
company.
I understand.
I'll increase the amount
on the bill.
Then when I receive the payment,
I will transfer
the difference into your account.
Well then, if you'll excuse me.
Hey! What's up?
Excuse me, what is this
emergency staff meeting for?
Looks like this time Onizuka-
sensei's really fired.
Really?
Yes, I couldn't believe it either.
It's Nakamaru-sensei who
brought this to our attention.
Yes, it seems the head teacher
hasn't been around recently.
I wonder if Onizuka did
something
- to the head teacher too.
- The head teacher too?
Did Onizuka do something
damaging to you too,
- Hakamada-sensei?
- Not you too, Kotani-sensei?
N-No, not really!
What about you,
Teshigawara-sensei?
- Oh well, no, I...
- Good morning.
Now, everyone.
The reason for today's
emergency meeting
is regarding Onizuka-sensei.
He attacked one of his
homeroom students.
This time's an major incident that
cannot be explained away.
If this leaked out to the media,
the status and future of this
academy will certainly be finished.
Nakamaru-sensei is really
into this.
He thinks he's head teacher
already.
No matter how much
the director covers for him,
I will never forgive that totally
unqualified
to be a teacher of a man.
Today, without question,
I will have Onizuka-sensei quit.
Thank you!
- Let me give you a hand.
- Oh...
Thanks!
MEIKEN SHOSEKI
In other business,
concerning the texts we will
begin using this fall...
I have studied the offerings
carefully.
I have found a source we can
trust completely.
- What are you doing?
- Stop it!
Please hold on.
Stop it! What are you doing?
- Please stop!
- What is he up to?
Stop it!
Please stop it! I'll call the police!
Please stop!
Will you please stop!
Stop it!
Please stop!
Who are you?
I'm your daughter's homeroom
teacher, Onizuka Eikichi.
Chikako...
What are you doing?
Stop it! Wait, please!
No, you're not...
How could you...
Do you realize what you
are doing, Onizuka?
You'll be fired, if you do this,
you'll be fired immediately!
There's no way you can
weasel out of this!
What... What's that?
Chikako, you didn't...
It's because you did this!
What's the meaning of this,
Ôshima-san?
I didn't want to do this either.
Not this...
But, but with this recession,
sales figures haven't risen.
If I don't show results,
I'll be restructured.
So I didn't have a choice.
You see, all this...
It was because I felt I had
to do it for you.
Don't try to make it
for our good.
Don't say it was for our family!
Don't make it an excuse!
Chikako,
don't get carried away.
You may be saying how
dirty adults are,
but take a look at yourself.
If you continue, you'll become
a dirty adult too.
Hold it!
Is this okay?
Sir, get a grip!
Why are you just standing there?
I figured it would turn
out like this.
It was too much
for Nakamaru-sensei.
He doesn't understand
a thing about Onizuka.
About the new texts, it's been
taken care of already, right?
Yes, well, there were
many mistakes...
I would like to look into it further.
Oh? I see.
- If you'll excuse me...
- Okay.
- Nakamaru-sensei.
- Yes?
Wasn't there something
regarding Onizuka-sensei
that you wanted to discuss
with me?
That's also still being
investigated.
Oh. I see.
Excuse me.
Nakamaru-sensei.
- Yes?
- Then...
Just now, were you
baking yakiimo?
Did you seriously tell them?
If you just kept your
mouths shut,
then it would have been
all his fault
and he would have been fired.
- So why did you tell the truth?
- We were the ones at fault!
- We had to apologize.
- Are you stupid?
Don't you care if you're
expelled?
We didn't want to become
dirty adults.
Both of us.
Don't worry, we won't
snitch about you.
But in return,
we're not going to associate
with the likes of you.
You think that's going
to solve everything?
Don't blame me if you regret it!
MUSASHINO SEIRIN  ACADEMY
Thanks for telling the truth,
you're great!
Don't worry about a thing,
you won't be expelled.
Really?
Trust your homeroom teacher!
Excuse us!
Sweet dreams!
- Is it okay to tell them that?
- Why's that?
This is going to be reported
to the head teacher, right?
It's possible they might
be expelled.
No way! When it comes to that,
I'll protect them!
Oh, hello Head Teacher!
You...
Did you think I would
ever approve?
- What's up with him?
- I'll get you out of here.
From this academy, no!
This town, no!
From the entire
educational system!
Did something happen?
- Oh, yes, yes, yes, I understand.
- President!
I'll discuss this with you
later then.
So you are Onizuka-sensei?
Who're you?
She's Aizawa Miyabi's mother,
the President of the PTA.
So, you're the one responsible
for getting my daughter
into so many bad situations?
I won't let you get away
with this now!
2016-05